[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "And be honest, when you knew you'd won the bid and you saw the Beijing Olympics' opening ceremony, did you think, what the hell are we going to do to beat that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "be", "honest", ",", "when", "you", "knew", "you", "'d", "won", "the", "bid", "and", "you", "saw", "the", "Beijing", "Olympics", "'", "opening", "ceremony", ",", "did", "you", "think", ",", "what", "the", "hell", "are", "we", "going", "to", "do", "to", "beat", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Beijing"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "But also just generally in that region?", "question_tokens": ["But", "also", "just", "generally", "in", "that", "region", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Well, it's a very good question and a very difficult one to answer.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "question", "and", "a", "very", "difficult", "one", "to", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How concerned should people be about the spread of the influence of the Muslim Brotherhood?", "question_tokens": ["How", "concerned", "should", "people", "be", "about", "the", "spread", "of", "the", "influence", "of", "the", "Muslim", "Brotherhood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "MD", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well, I think, first of all, we have to understand what's going on in the region.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "we", "have", "to", "understand", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "in", "the", "region", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "How much do you agree with Israel's fear and concern about the nature of Iran's threat?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "agree", "with", "Israel", "'s", "fear", "and", "concern", "about", "the", "nature", "of", "Iran", "'s", "threat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Essentially, I mean, I agree that a nuclear armed Iran is a devastating thing for the region.", "answer_tokens": ["Essentially", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "agree", "that", "a", "nuclear", "armed", "Iran", "is", "a", "devastating", "thing", "for", "the", "region", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "And if Israel decides to act unilaterally, which they have threatened to do, where would that leave everybody in the Middle East?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "Israel", "decides", "to", "act", "unilaterally", ",", "which", "they", "have", "threatened", "to", "do", ",", "where", "would", "that", "leave", "everybody", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, the first thing to understand is Israel will protect its own interest.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "thing", "to", "understand", "is", "Israel", "will", "protect", "its", "own", "interest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Because there's a general acceptance that Assad must go, but how is he going to go?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "there", "'s", "a", "general", "acceptance", "that", "Assad", "must", "go", ",", "but", "how", "is", "he", "going", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "It's -- it's very, very difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "very", ",", "very", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "How is the special relationship in reality do you think between America and Britain these days?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "the", "special", "relationship", "in", "reality", "do", "you", "think", "between", "America", "and", "Britain", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "I think it's still strong.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "still", "strong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "How are you reading the political ruins at the moment in Washington?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "reading", "the", "political", "ruins", "at", "the", "moment", "in", "Washington", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Look, if the American elections for you guys is not for us guys.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "if", "the", "American", "elections", "for", "you", "guys", "is", "not", "for", "us", "guys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "How perilous is the situation when you look at Europe in totality?", "question_tokens": ["How", "perilous", "is", "the", "situation", "when", "you", "look", "at", "Europe", "in", "totality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Deeply perilous.", "answer_tokens": ["Deeply", "perilous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Europe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "And should it be saved?", "question_tokens": ["And", "should", "it", "be", "saved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "But is it an exaggeration to say that in her hands, the future, certainly in the short term and middle term of the whole European economy could rest on what Germany does?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "an", "exaggeration", "to", "say", "that", "in", "her", "hands", ",", "the", "future", ",", "certainly", "in", "the", "short", "term", "and", "middle", "term", "of", "the", "whole", "European", "economy", "could", "rest", "on", "what", "Germany", "does", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "I think it does rest on what Germany does, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "does", "rest", "on", "what", "Germany", "does", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Well, I don't -- you know -- look, I don't want to enter into a controversy that must be difficult for people in America right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "you", "know", "--", "look", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "enter", "into", "a", "controversy", "that", "must", "be", "difficult", "for", "people", "in", "America", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "But do you think, though, that high-powered assault weapons and magazine drums capable of unloading a hundred bullets a minute, is it right that they should still be legally accessible?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", ",", "though", ",", "that", "high-powered", "assault", "weapons", "and", "magazine", "drums", "capable", "of", "unloading", "a", "hundred", "bullets", "a", "minute", ",", "is", "it", "right", "that", "they", "should", "still", "be", "legally", "accessible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "I think the Americans have got to decide this.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "Americans", "have", "got", "to", "decide", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "How do you do it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I work out a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "work", "out", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Every day, is it?", "question_tokens": ["Every", "day", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Not every day.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "But what it comes your way again?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "it", "comes", "your", "way", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Let's wait and see if it does.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "wait", "and", "see", "if", "it", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "When you look back over your whole career, if I could let you relive one moment of success again, what one moment would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "over", "your", "whole", "career", ",", "if", "I", "could", "let", "you", "relive", "one", "moment", "of", "success", "again", ",", "what", "one", "moment", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "CD", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, you rarely get moments of success.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "rarely", "get", "moments", "of", "success", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "What would be the things you'd like to talk to him about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "be", "the", "things", "you", "'d", "like", "to", "talk", "to", "him", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Well, I think it's got a huge challenge for itself and for the world.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "got", "a", "huge", "challenge", "for", "itself", "and", "for", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Why would you do that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "For the sake of Pakistan.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "the", "sake", "of", "Pakistan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "It was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "RBR", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Has the Afghanistan war been successful or has it, arguably, made Pakistan even more understandable and even more dangerous?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "the", "Afghanistan", "war", "been", "successful", "or", "has", "it", ",", "arguably", ",", "made", "Pakistan", "even", "more", "understandable", "and", "even", "more", "dangerous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Well, I think it has made Pakistan more dangerous now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "has", "made", "Pakistan", "more", "dangerous", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan", "Pakistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "What does Pakistan do about that, to try and rebuild that trust?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "Pakistan", "do", "about", "that", ",", "to", "try", "and", "rebuild", "that", "trust", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Yes, that -- I totally agree with you, that it is not believable.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "--", "I", "totally", "agree", "with", "you", ",", "that", "it", "is", "not", "believable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Is that -- is that likely?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "--", "is", "that", "likely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "-- that he might be?", "question_tokens": ["--", "that", "he", "might", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "When you hear Mitt Romney, who may well be president come November, talking of Iran being the most dangerous place on Earth now and the prospect of them getting nuclear weapons making it even more dangerous, what is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "who", "may", "well", "be", "president", "come", "November", ",", "talking", "of", "Iran", "being", "the", "most", "dangerous", "place", "on", "Earth", "now", "and", "the", "prospect", "of", "them", "getting", "nuclear", "weapons", "making", "it", "even", "more", "dangerous", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VB", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't call it the most dangerous place in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "call", "it", "the", "most", "dangerous", "place", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Iran", "Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "So why go nuclear?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "go", "nuclear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Well, Iran would argue they do have threats.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Iran", "would", "argue", "they", "do", "have", "threats", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Iran"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "I mean if Israel is allowed nuclear weapons, if Pakistan are, if you're in Iran, Ahmadinejad, he would argue -- I've heard him say this -- if these other countries are allowed to have nuclear weapons, why can't I?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "if", "Israel", "is", "allowed", "nuclear", "weapons", ",", "if", "Pakistan", "are", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "in", "Iran", ",", "Ahmadinejad", ",", "he", "would", "argue", "--", "I", "'ve", "heard", "him", "say", "this", "--", "if", "these", "other", "countries", "are", "allowed", "to", "have", "nuclear", "weapons", ",", "why", "ca", "n't", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Well -- well, first of all, Israel doesn't have a border with Iran.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--", "well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "Israel", "does", "n't", "have", "a", "border", "with", "Iran", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Pakistan", "Iran", "Ahmadinejad"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Isn't there a -- a moral compulsion now to get in there?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "there", "a", "--", "a", "moral", "compulsion", "now", "to", "get", "in", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Well, I think so much has happened in -- in interfering in various countries of the Muslim world, I would say, that I think that external interference has never produced good results.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "so", "much", "has", "happened", "in", "--", "in", "interfering", "in", "various", "countries", "of", "the", "Muslim", "world", ",", "I", "would", "say", ",", "that", "I", "think", "that", "external", "interference", "has", "never", "produced", "good", "results", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan", "Pakistan"]}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ":", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Who would you prefer to win?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "prefer", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Well, I would like to -- generally in Pakistan, people believe that Republicans have always been favorably disposed toward Pakistan, more than the Democrats.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "like", "to", "--", "generally", "in", "Pakistan", ",", "people", "believe", "that", "Republicans", "have", "always", "been", "favorably", "disposed", "toward", "Pakistan", ",", "more", "than", "the", "Democrats", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "So you're a -- you're a Romney man?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "a", "--", "you", "'re", "a", "Romney", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Well, no, not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", ",", "not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "But from all you've seen and heard of President Obama and Mitt Romney, which one do you think would best suit the interests of Pakistan over the next four years?", "question_tokens": ["But", "from", "all", "you", "'ve", "seen", "and", "heard", "of", "President", "Obama", "and", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "which", "one", "do", "you", "think", "would", "best", "suit", "the", "interests", "of", "Pakistan", "over", "the", "next", "four", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "CD", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Difficult question to answer.", "answer_tokens": ["Difficult", "question", "to", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Pakistan"]}}]